def get_question(question_num):

  if question_num == 1:
    question = {
      "question": "3x^2-3x-1=x^2+1",
      "correct": "(2x+1)(x-2)",
      "incorrect": "(x+1)(x+2)"
    }

  if question_num == 2:
    question = {
      "question": "x^2+2x=0",
      "correct": "x(x+2)=0",
      "incorrect": "(x-1)(x+2)"
    }
    
  if question_num == 3:
    question = {
      "question": "Sin/Cos",
      "correct": "tan",
      "incorrect": "cot"
    }
    
  if question_num == 4:
    question = {
      "question": "1/sin(x)",
      "correct": "csc(x)",
      "incorrect": "sec(x)"
    }
    
  if question_num == 5:
    question = {
      "question": "(x-4)(x+2)=0",
      "correct": "x=4, x=-2",
      "incorrect": "x=-4, x=-2"
    }
    
  if question_num == 6:
    question = {
      "question": "3^4/3^2",
      "correct": 9,
      "incorrect": 12
    }
    
  if question_num == 7:
    question = {
      "question": "4904^0:",
      "correct": 1,
      "incorrect": 0
    }
    
  if question_num == 8:
    question = {
      "question": "What is m in y=mx+b",
      "correct": "slope",
      "incorrect": "x-intercept"
    }
    
  if question_num == 9:
    question = {
      "question": "5x(x+8)=0",
      "correct": "x=0,x=-8",
      "incorrect": "x=-1,x=8"
    }
    
  if question_num == 10:
    question = {
      "question": "one radian in degrees",
      "correct": 57.29,
      "incorrect": 60.23
    }
    
  if question_num == 11:
    question = {
      "question": "√196",
      "correct": 14,
      "incorrect": 18
    }

  if question_num == 12:
    question = {
      "question": "n^2+7n+6",
      "correct": "(n+6),n+1)",
      "incorrect": "(n-6),(n-1)"
    }
    
  if question_num == 13:
    question = {
      "question": "y-intercept for sin(x)",
      "correct": "0",
      "incorrect": "1"
    }
    
  if question_num == 14:
    question = {
      "question": "y-intercept for cos(x)",
      "correct": 1,
      "incorrect": 0
    }
    
  if question_num == 15:
    question = {
      "question": "√-4",
      "correct": 'imaginary number',
      "incorrect": -2
    }
    
  if question_num == 16:
    question = {
      "question": "18% de 50:",
      "correct": 9,
      "incorrect": 18
    }
    
  if question_num == 17:
    question = {
      "question": "Select the prime number",
      "correct": 17,
      "incorrect": 51
    }
    
  if question_num == 18:
    question = {
      "question": "next number in 2,4,16...",
      "correct": "256",
      "incorrect": "64"
    }
    
  if question_num == 19:
    question = {
      "question": "x^-6",
      "correct": '1/x^6',
      "incorrect": 'imaginary number'
    }
    
  if question_num == 20:
    question = {
      "question": "derivative of 26",
      "correct": "0",
      "incorrect": "26x"
    }
    
  if question_num == 21:
    question = {
      "question": "(x+3)^2=49",
      "correct": "x=-10,x=4",
      "incorrect": "x=-10,x=4"
    }

  if question_num == 22:
    question = {
      "question": "4!",
      "correct": 24,
      "incorrect": 100
    }
    
  if question_num == 23:
    question = {
      "question": "anti-derivartve of 30x",
      "correct": "15x^2",
      "incorrect": "30x/2"
    }
    
  if question_num == 24:
    question = {
      "question": "derivative of e^2x",
      "correct": '2e^2x',
      "incorrect": 'e^2x'
    }
    
  if question_num == 25:
    question = {
      "question": "4^2/4^1",
      "correct": 4,
      "incorrect": 16
    }
    
  if question_num == 26:
    question = {
      "question": "derivative of ln(5x)",
      "correct": "1/x",
      "incorrect": "5x^2/5x"
    }
    
  if question_num == 27:
    question = {
      "question": "if tanA 2/3, sinA=",
      "correct": "2√13",
      "incorrect": "3√14"
    }
    
  if question_num == 28:
    question = {
      "question": "tangent",
      "correct": "opposite/adjacent",
      "incorrect": "opposite/hypotenuse"
    }
    
  if question_num == 29:
    question = {
      "question": "derivative of 4x^2+5x+20",
      "correct": "8x+5",
      "incorrect": "6x^2+2"
    }
    
  if question_num == 30:
    question = {
      "question": "deriva 3x+2",
      "correct": 3,
      "incorrect": 2
    }
   
  return question
